# Nguyen Thi Chi Lam

**GAME DATA ANALYST** 



**Date of birth** 15/10/2001

**Gender** Female

Address
District 5, Ho Chi Minh City

**Phone** 0967423249

Email nguyenlam151001@gmail.com

Website linkedin.com/in/lâm-nguyễn-a42b31286

## **Objective**

Apply data analysis skills to explore player behavior, optimize game performance, and propose strategies to improve user experience. Desire to learn and develop in a professional environment, contributing to creating better quality and more engaging game products.

## **Skills**

- Data Analysis and Visualization: PowerBl, Excel
- Programming: Python, SQL
- Project Management: Jira, Trello
- Stakeholder Engagement & Communication
- Soft Skills: Analytical Thinking, Problem-Solving, Communication and Collaboration

## **Activities**

June 2020 - Sep 2020

Manga Trans & Edit Team

Volunteer Translator

May 2020 - Jun 2020

**UIT SAFE Volunteer** 

Participate in the volunteer movement to measure the temperature of students, lecturers and visitors to UIT during the Covid19 outbreak.

Dec 2019

**UIT ENGLISH SPEAKING CONTEST** 

Participate in the English contest about the era of technological development.

# **Certifications**

TOEIC Certificate (Score 835) | 2024

## **Experience**

Dec 2024 - Present

#### FREELANCE RESEARCH ANALYST

- Collect and research scientific articles related to Quality of Accounting Information Systems (QAIS).
- Analyze survey data using SPSS, perform Exploratory Factor Analysis (EFA) and calculate Cronbach's Alpha to test the reliability of the data.
- Support research for thesis on QAIS in enterprise.

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

#### CJ OLIVENETWORKS VINA

**BUSINESS ANALYST & QA TESTER INTERN** 

#### **Business Analyst:**

- Analyzed As-is business processes and suggested improvements.
- Designed a user-friendly contract management screen.
- Defined business requirements and documented workflows using Jira/Confluence.

#### **QA Tester:**

- Developed test cases and conducted functional testing.
- Reported and tracked software defects in Jira, collaborating with developers to improve product quality.

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

### **CAT MARKET RESEARCH & ADVISOR**

- Researched and observed market trends, breed popularity, and buyer preferences.
- Evaluate regional prices and demand based on experience and observations.
- Advise customers on appropriate breed selection and basic care.
- Negotiate reasonable prices between buyers and sellers.

### **Education**

Oct 2019 - Nov 2024

# UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY - UIT Major: Information System

- Relevant coursework: Statistical Analysis, System Analysis & Design, Intelligent Applications & Decision Support, Data Mining
- Graduation Project: Forecasting gold price based on machine learning.